{
    "subject": "Jessica_Buchanan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Nash_Brennan",
    "human_readable": "Jessica Buchanan is married to Nash Brennan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9352665543556213,
            "question": "Name the person married to Nash Brennan."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9186426401138306,
            "question": "Who is married to Nash Brennan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9120075702667236,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Jessica Buchanan and Nash Brennan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9013481140136719,
            "question": "To whom is Jessica Buchanan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8629501461982727,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Jessica Buchanan and Nash Brennan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7733010053634644,
            "question": "Who are Jessica Buchanan and Nash Brennan to each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7211373448371887,
            "question": "What is the name of Nash Brennan's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6816502213478088,
            "question": "Who is Jessica Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.649175226688385,
            "question": "Is Jessica Buchanan in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6297099590301514,
            "question": "Is Jessica Buchanan's marital status known?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jessica Buchanan is married to Nash Brennan.",
            "html": "yago_30421_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Jessica Buchanan in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_30421_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Jessica Buchanan?",
            "html": "yago_30421_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Nash Brennan's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30421_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30421_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Jessica Buchanan is married to Nash Brennan\":\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the documents, Jessica and Nash were \"finally together\" but it's not explicitly stated as a marriage. In fact, in the document with file path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30421/re-ranker-msmarco/81.txt, it is mentioned that Nash Brennan and Jessica Buchanan had a \"dissolved\" marital relationship."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Jessica Buchanan and Nash Brennan were married, though their marriage was dissolved. Given the context provided in the documents, it supports the statement that Jessica Buchanan is married (or previously married) to Nash Brennan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}